merial.com 2011-11-25

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is designed to inform you about Merial's practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information (includes information that could be used to identify you, such as your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, etc.) that you may provide through your access to or usage of the Site. 

## Consent

Merial does not collect personal information about you except when you voluntarily provide it. Whenever you provide either optional or required information through your access to or usage of the Site, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of that information in accordance with the provisions of this Privacy Policy.

## When we collect your personal information

Personal information may be collected in a number of instances. For example, this Site contains areas that collect information from its visitors through feedback data, such as questions, comments and suggestions. Some of the information that you provide through feedback data may be personal information. In addition, access to certain areas of the Site is restricted. In order to apply for access to these restricted areas, you are required to submit a registration application form which may include personal information. Further, some areas of the Site require you to submit information which may include personal information in order to benefit from specified features (such as newsletters, e-commerce/order processing). You will be informed at each collection point what information is required and what information is optional. 

Merial may also collect information about you and your use of the Site through the use of "cookies." Cookies are small data files that are sent to your browser and stored on your computer's hard-drive when you visit certain websites, thereby "tracking" use of the site. Some browsers can be set to reject all cookies; if you choose to modify your browser in this manner, some pages of the Site may not function properly. Merial uses the information generated through the use of cookies to estimate the number of people that are using the Site and to track the pages of the Site that are being visited. This information tells Merial about user interests and behaviors which can, in turn, be used to provide you with information about products, services, features or promotions that may be of interest to you.

## Use of information

Merial uses your personal information to improve the content of the Site, to customize the Site to your preferences, to create a profile relating to you in order to show you content that may be of interest to you, to provide the services and features requested by you and, if you ask us to, to send you information about products, services, features or promotions that may be of interest to you. 

Merial may also use your personal information to create aggregated information that does not allow you to be personally identified or contacted. Rather than showing individual activity, aggregated information shows user behaviour as a whole. Aggregated information is used for Site development and to market and promote the Site. 

## When we disclose your personal information

Merial may disclose your personal information to those of its affiliates and related companies that agree to treat it substantially in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Merial will not, without your permission, disclose your personal information to unaffiliated third parties except that Merial reserves the right to disclose your personal information to: (i) third party service providers for purposes related to supporting our business (e.g. fulfilment services, technical support, delivery services) and providing you with information that may be of interest to you (if you have requested to receive such information as described above) in which case Merial will require such third parties to agree to treat it substantially in accordance with this Privacy Policy; and (ii) to third parties in connection with the sale, assignment or other transfer of the business of this Site to which the information relates, in which case Merial will require any such buyer, assignee or transferee to agree to treat it substantially in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

Merial will otherwise only release your personal information to third parties in the following limited circumstances and to the extent permitted by law: (i) if a law, regulation, search warrant, subpoena or court order permits or requires it to do so; (ii) if the rights or property of Merial, its affiliates or related companies, third party service providers or the users of the Site are in jeopardy; or (iii) if the personal safety of users of the Site or other members of the public are in jeopardy. 

Merial may disclose aggregated information that does not allow you to be personally identified to its affiliates and related companies and to unaffiliated third parties. 

## How we protect your personal information

Recognizing that your privacy is important to you, Merial employs technical security measures to protect your personal information. However, no transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure. Consequently, to the extent permitted by law, Merial, its affiliates and related companies, third party service providers and their respective officers, directors, employees and agents do not represent, warrant or guarantee that personal information will be protected against misuse, loss or alterations and do not accept any liability arising from the submission of any personal information or from any third parties' use or misuse of personal information.

The information you provide to Merial via the Internet is password-protected for your privacy and security. Merial uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology in transmitting such information to our servers to help ensure the integrity and privacy of the information. Encryption involves systematically scrambling numbers and letters, so that even if someone managed to intercept the information, they would not be able to make sense of it. In order to take advantage of this encryption technology, you need to have an Internet browser that will support encryption, such as Firefox or Internet Explorer. As an additional security measure, the information you provide via the Internet is also kept physically separate on a separate server where your password is encrypted and stored on a database. 

## Links to other Websites

You should be aware that operators of linked websites may also collect your personal information (including information generated through the use of cookies) when you link to their websites. Merial is not responsible for how such third parties collect, use or disclose your personal information, so you should check their privacy policies before providing them with your personal information.

## Changes

Merial reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time by notifying you by posting the changes on this Site, and you are advised to review this page regularly for any changes. This Privacy Policy was last amended on April 2, 2011.

## Other Terms

Your use of this Site is subject to the terms and conditions set forth in the Legal Notification section. By accessing or using the Site, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions in effect at the time of your access or use, including this Privacy Policy.

## Contacting Us

You can contact Merial at 888-Merial 1 to request access to your personal information or to request that Merial update your personal information. If you believe that Merial has failed to adhere to this Privacy Policy, please contact Merial at 888-Merial 1.
